If you have any type of
car which you want to insure yourself
from your mobile, then in today's
video I am going to tell you
how you
can insure your car from your mobile sitting at home, I will
tell you that in this video, so
let's start, so everyone my name is
Vijay and you are watching Vijay Solution, so first of all let me
tell you that if you
want to insure your car, then for that
you should have your vehicle number,
apart from this you should have your PAN card and if you have Aadhar
card then it is good or Voter ID
card, any one proof, you will have to give address
proof, so if you have all these
things then let me tell you how you will do the insurance,
for that first of all you need a
website, so where will you get the link of the website
because you people will go and
direct it,
like you will click here in this
way, you will get the option here, you have to click on it,
as soon as you click on it, in
this way you will reach this website,
you people always have to do the
insurance from this website
so that in future also, suppose
tomorrow someone  If there is an accident for a claim
or you need any help, then I should have the
details and I should be able to help you completely,
so you have to come in this way,
after coming here you just have to enter your car
number here,
car number means the
number of your car which is on the number plate,
you have to give it here, so
whatever the number of the car will be, it will be
written on the number plate, you have to see
that and click on view price here, as soon as
you click on this,
all the details of the vehicle will be
automatically picked up, which
variant model it is, which variant it is, how it is,
all those details come here, you do
n't have to do anything, it is simple, you are being
asked for the details of your policy here,
so I will give it, it is saying that it is getting
deregistered, you have to
tell me the date on which it is expiring,
let me tell you, for that I
click on the calendar here,
suppose I am giving it today's date,
so I have now clicked here  I will come down here,
here the insurance company is being
asked, whichever company it is,
you will enter it here and after that what
you have to do is come directly down
and here you will see the pay view code,
click on it, as soon as you click on it, it will appear like this
and here
you will get to see the list of all the companies available here, you
can see here the list of all the companies
which are
ready to insure your car, so here in
front of the list name of all the companies you
will see that the price is written here,
okay, so if you do United then it will cost
you this much rupees, if you do Digit then it will cost
you 2076, similarly if you
do Oriental then it will cost 3036, so in this
way you will know here that
if you want to insure your car, then
how much will the insurance cost
you and the rate which is
shown here shows the final rate, meaning it is
not going to cost you even ₹1 more than this, so
you can choose whichever one you like from this here
now  There are a few things
that you have to pay attention to here,
so first of all suppose your IDV is
showing 240000 here, then you
can increase it as well, this IDV means the
value of your vehicle, if tomorrow your
vehicle meets with an accident or
your vehicle gets stolen or destroyed in some way, then in such a case the
insurance company will
give that much amount, if you feel that this IDV is
showing less, then what will you do, here you will
see the ID option,
you will click on it and here it will be at
the minimum, you
will click on choose and after this you can make it
full by holding it from here or if
you have any fix that I want to keep this much, then you
can also write it here, I will make it
full here and
click on update, then you will see that it will get
updated automatically, as soon as it comes now you
can see that what was 25 lakhs has now
reached ₹ lakh, okay, so in this way
you can see all the on damage, if you
come down then here  For example, suppose
you are seeing it as expensive at the top, then if
you go down, you will see it as cheaper as well, so
whichever you find best, what I mean to say is that it is
not that you have to spend a lot of money, you will go for the one which is the
lowest priced and has a good ID,
if you take my advice, you
can see here that it is writing ₹ 69000 here
and is doing 000, so it is very expensive,
so here if we
come down a little from that, then it is doing it for only 3500 for 27000, for
33572, so
why won't you do this one, okay, so what is there here is that
you get the complete list, you do whatever you
find best, okay, now suppose this
digit seems right to me because the
rate is also coming correct, then
if I want to insure it simply, then
I will click on it here, as if I
click on this, many times the name comes automatically here,
if it does not come then you have to give your name,
meaning your name means the person in
whose name the car is  You have to give his name
here, let me give it, I will
enter the mobile number,
here I will give the email ID, whatever the
email ID is and after giving this email ID,
now what I am doing here is I am
looking for next, I am clicking on it,
after which it will come in this way,
you have to click on next here,
after which you will be asked for address, whatever
your address is, you have to write that complete address
here and after that you will
click on next, now after that it comes
here for KYC,
first of all you have to give the date of birth
here, you have to give the date of birth which will be in the PAN card,
for that first of all you have to
choose the year from here, in whichever year you were
born, you have to choose the year here,
you have to choose the month here and
choose the date here, whatever date
you were born and after that it will be on
KYC, you have to click
by PAN number and here you have to
give your PAN card number, let me
give my PAN card number and
after doing this  Here I am seeing submit, I am
clicking on it, this KYC has now become
necessary, now you can see that
after my KYC it has automatically come here that you have to make a payment of Rs. 33572, now
what you have to do is simple, you will
get the option of Pay Secure below, you
will click on it, as if you click on Pay Secure, it will
come like this, now you have to make this
payment, so if you have an ATM
card and want to make payment through it, then
go to this option, if you want to make payment through credit card, then on
this one you
get all the options, net banking, UPI, nowadays most of the people
have UPI, so they want to make UPI
like,
suppose
you have to choose the first one separately, or if
you click on this, then the scanner will come like this
and in this also you will see,
your UPID is written here, so
you can copy it from here and it will be
copied on this one, so by doing this
you have to come back to your page and
paste it here, as if you paste it, it will
come completely, so you have to
delete the initial one till the rate  You have to pay because
you do not have to choose @ the rate in this, you have to
choose the rate in this, so ours is this one after the rate, so
I choose it and
after that you are looking at 357 213, you have to
click on it, as soon as you click on it,
something like this will appear, now what you have to do is if you
look above,
a notification will automatically appear in this way, you
can see here,
you will simply click on download and you will
get the PDF of your policy copy, after
printing it, it will
work in original form, so in this way,
you can easily do your car insurance
in minutes with the help of your mobile, if there is any
problem or any issue,
then my mobile number is given below,
you can call on that and ask, for
now, that's all in this video,
thank you very much.